CHRISTY: I'm just saying you can take the
damn plastic off the couch once in a while.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Why, so you
and Howard can hump on it?
HOWARD: Ladies, ladies,
I'm sure there's a middle ground.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Shut up, Howard!
CHRISTY: Shut up, Howard!
HOWARD: You guys talk.
I'm gonna take my scooter out for a spin.
CHRISTY: You happy?
You drove your son out of the house.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Why don't you stop butting in?
- What are you guys doing here?
- It's "Halo" night.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
He's not a man, he's a putz.
(Howard's Mother(voice):)And don't you take that tone with me,
you gold digger.
CHRISTY: What'd you call me?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: You heard me.
(Howard's Mother(voice):)You're barking up the wrong tree...
...because as long as you're around,
Howard is out of the will.
CHRISTY: You know what?
I got better offers. I'm out of here.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: That's right.
Go back to Babylon, you whore.
So "Halo" night, huh?
- I thought she was the whore of Omaha.
- Shh.
[GUNFIRE ON TV]